

# Suriyan Jaisankar UX/UI Designer

**Contact** 

+91 94427 92005

• Vellore, Tamil Nadu, India

M suriyan.jaisankar@gmail.com

in Linked In: Suriyan Jaisankar

### **About Me**

I am Suriyan Jaisankar, passionate and enthusiastic UX UI Designer from the Fort City of Tamil Nadu (Vellore), with Undergrads in Mechanical Engineering from VIT **University**, Vellore, India. Most of the times, the ability to perceive is proportional to the quality of understanding, and the quality of outcome. In my case, before this transition into UX UI Design field, I had undergone the Civil service preparation journey which had enhanced my perception by multiple folds. Using that to my fullest advantage, along with professional training in UX UI Design from a reputed Institute, I strive to satisfy my hunger by being a part of the teams in Companies that are tirelessly creating delightful digital experiences and products.

## Languages

Tamil, English, & Hindi.

#### **Hobbies**









Adventure Touring

Experiencing Cinema Reading

Swimming

# #KeySkills

#Design Thinking, #UX Research, #UX Design,#UI Design, #Heuristic Evaluation, #Figma,#AdobeXD, #Wireframing, #Prototyping,#Visual Design, #Graphic Design, #Website Design,#AR/VR/MR/XR Designing

#### **Toolbox**









Canva

## Experience

2022-2023

Brandlution Internship | Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

**Education** 

2022-2023

Post Graduate Program in UX/UI Design,

PGP in UX/UI

from Digital Academy 360, Bengaluru.

2017-2021

Attempted **Civil Service Exams** 3 Times

2013-2016

**Mechanical Engineering** from Vellore Institute of Technology University, Vellore, **79.3%** in B. Tech Mechanical

2011-2012

Lakshmi Garden Matric Higher Secondary School, Vellore **83.5%** in HSC

2009-2010

Lakshmi Garden Matric Higher Secondary School, Vellore **92%** in SSLC

# **Projects**

Checkout my Behance profile for my recent UX UI Case studies

SCAN this **QR** 

or

Click this Link

